titlecapitalization.com 2016-11-01

# TitleCap Privacy Policy

1\. Introduction 

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how Titlecapitalization.com ("Titlecapitalization.com") collects, uses and discloses information from and about visitors to and users of Titlecapitalization.com, including unregistered visitors ("Visitors"), registered members ("Members") and registered non-subscription guests ("Guests"), as each category is further described in the Terms of Use, and what choices Members, Guests and Visitors each have regarding the collection and use of such information. This Privacy Policy also explains procedures for the security and protection of the information collected and how you can access and update your information. By accessing the Titlecapitalization.com website ("Website") as a Visitor, Member, or Guest, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy, including Titlecapitalization.com policies with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal and non-personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

2\. Information Collected 

Titlecapitalization.com collects and stores certain personally identifiable information about you when you provide it to us during registration (or when you update your account information), when you use or subscribe to Titlecapitalization.com services, including when you respond to Titlecapitalization.com surveys or submit content or materials to Titlecapitalization.com, or when you otherwise communicate with Titlecapitalization.com, such as through emails. The type of personally identifiable information collected may include your name, email address, demographic information, and other personal information, depending upon the particular Titlecapitalization.com service, the information requested and provided, and the category of user. Titlecapitalization.com also collects and stores certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit and use the Website or otherwise interact with Titlecapitalization.com, including using Titlecapitalization.com services, submitting content or materials to Titlecapitalization.com, and responding to surveys and email communications. The type of non-personal information collected may include your computer and internet connection information, including IP address and operating system, and your usage history of the Website and its web pages. This non-personal information may be gathered by using "cookies" and/or "clear GIF" (Graphical Interchange Format) technologies, as well as login file information. "Cookies" are small data files with a unique identifier that we transfer to your computerâ€™s hard drive or web browser, that collect and store data about your visit to the Website. This allows our systems to identify you when you return to the Website and to analyze your Website usage. "GIFs" are small graphic files with a unique identifier contained in our Website that we use to track Website traffic. This allows us to monitor and improve the performance of the Website and the related services offered, and to collect and use the information as described in this Privacy Policy. This non-personally identifiable information will be treated in the same fashion, and in aggregate to, all information provided by a Member, Guest, or Visitor. 

3\. Use of Information 

Titlecapitalization.com uses your personal and non-personal information in order to improve and personalize your use of the Website and its related products and services, including by tracking and monitoring traffic on the Website so as to enhance the performance of the Website. Titlecapitalization.com does not share your personal information with third parties, except to the extent necessary to process transactions with you, for example, credit card processing companies, or in the case of contests that include a third party partner, or promotional offers. However, Titlecapitalization.com may disclose any such information pursuant to law, including subpoena, warrants or other orders; in order to enforce the Terms of Use or other Website policies and rules with respect to a particular Titlecapitalization.com product or service, including reporting suspected cheating or intellectual property rights violations, or any other related agreements between you and Titlecapitalization.com; or as otherwise may be required to protect the rights of Titlecapitalization.com, its directors, officers, representatives and agents, or its Members, Guests or Visitors. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, Titlecapitalization.com may share some or all of your personal information with another entity in the event of a change in business structure, including merger or acquisition, as well as with the representatives of the entity to the extent required. Except as described above, Titlecapitalization.com will not disclose any personal information about you to third parties without your permission. We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users. As a user or guest, you may access and update your personal information as described in the Terms of Use, however, information originally submitted to Titlecapitalization.com by you may be retained by Titlecapitalization.com for technical, legal, or other reasons. 

4\. General Limitations 

This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use. Titlecapitalization.com may revise or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and it is your responsibility to regularly review this Privacy Policy for any changes to it. If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Titlecapitalization.com or about this Privacy Policy, please Joe Lynn. Titlecapitalization.com implements reasonable steps to maintain the privacy and security of your information against unauthorized access consistent with industry standards, however, as with all online transactions, hackers or other third parties may intercept and misuse your personal information, including during transmission to and from the Website. The Website and its related products and services are not intended for use by children under 13 years of age and children under 13 may not submit personal information to Titlecapitalization.com. Titlecapitalization.com will not knowingly collect or use personal information of anyone under 13 years of age, and if Titlecapitalization.com is informed or determines that any such information has been submitted, it will be deleted.
